const constants = {
  COLORS: [
    "primary",
    "secondary",
    "primary",
    "secondary",
    "primary",
    "secondary",
  ],
  IMAGES: [
    "https://media4.giphy.com/media/3o6fJcIM6mG3Ad6lAk/giphy.gif",
    "https://newyear2020s.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Wonderful-New-year-gif-for-whatsapp.gif",
    "https://i.pinimg.com/originals/b7/09/0f/b7090f7aafd788232d92acabbfc55c30.gif",
    "https://happynewyear.best/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/happy-new-year-gifs.gif",
    "https://i.pinimg.com/originals/56/44/d3/5644d37384433f934642616739a7ccd5.gif",
  ],
  QUESTIONS: [
    {
      question: "Do you know Crispen Gari?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Do you know Crispen Gari?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Crispen's favorite color?",
      answer1: "White",
      answer2: "Black",
      correct: "Black",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Crispen's favorite sport?",
      answer1: "Volleyball",
      answer2: "Football",
      correct: "Football",
    },
    {
      question: "Crispen loves dogs more than cats!",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Which programming language does Crispen loves the most?",
      answer1: "Python",
      answer2: "C++",
      correct: "Python",
    },
    {
      question: "Which programming language does crispen knows the most?",
      answer1: "Python",
      answer2: "JavaScript",
      correct: "JavaScript",
    },
    {
      question: "Is Crispen a Christian?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Which church does Crispen goes to?",
      answer1: "SDA",
      answer2: "Methodist",
      correct: "SDA",
    },
    {
      question: "Crispen loves the bible!",
      answer1: "True",
      answer2: "False",
      correct: "True",
    },
    {
      question: "Crispen is interested in girls!",
      answer1: "No",
      answer2: "Yes",
      correct: "No",
    },
    {
      question: "How old is Crispen?",
      answer1: "20",
      answer2: "21",
      correct: "21",
    },
    {
      question: "When was Crispen born?",
      answer1: "2000",
      answer2: "1999",
      correct: "1999",
    },
    {
      question: "Which month was Crispen born?",
      answer1: "October",
      answer2: "August",
      correct: "October",
    },
    {
      question: "Where's Crispen from?",
      answer1: "Zimbabwe",
      answer2: "South Africa",
      correct: "Zimbabwe",
    },
    {
      question: "Crispen spend most of his time doing what?",
      answer1: "Playing Games",
      answer2: "Programming",
      correct: "Programming",
    },
    {
      question: "Which frontend framework does Crispen loves the most?",
      answer1: "React",
      answer2: "Vue",
      correct: "React",
    },
    {
      question: "Which backend framework does Crispen loves the most?",
      answer1: "Django",
      answer2: "Node",
      correct: "Node",
    },
    {
      question: "What does Crispen loves most?",
      answer1: "Machine Learning",
      answer2: "Data Science",
      correct: "Machine Learning",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen loves You?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen loves God?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen love sleeping?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen loves Food?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "No",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen loves C++?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Crispen loves Java?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      correct: "Yes",
    },
  ],
};

export default constants;
